FOX NEWS OBTAINED A PHOTOGRAPH
OF THE DISPATCH ORDER SENT OUT
AFTER BORDER PATROL AGENTS CALLED
IN THAT THEY WERE UNDER ATTACK.
THE POLICE DEPARTMENT ISSUED A
STATEMENT YESTERDAY TRYING TO
WALK THE ORDER BACK SAYING CPD
OFFICERS DID IN FACT RESPOND TO
THAT SHOOTING SCENE INVOLVING
FEDERAL AUTHORITIES ON SATURDAY
TO MAINTAIN PUBLIC SAFETY AND
TRAFFIC CONTROL.
HOWEVER, TWO POLICE SOURCES TOLD
FOX NEWS THAT'S NOT TRUE.
TWO SUSPECTS WERE ARRESTED FOR
ALLEGEDLY RAMMING THEIR CARS AND
INVESTIGATING THEIR CARS AND
DHS SAYS ONE SUSPECT WAS FLAGGED
IN AN INTELLIGENCE BULLETIN LAST
WEEK FOR THREATENING AGENTS.
THIS WEEKEND SHE ALLEGEDLY
SIDESWIPED AN AGENT'S CAR AND WAS
CARRYING A GUN.
THAT AGENT, UNABLE TO ESCAPE, SHOT
AND INJURED HER.
BEFORE WE GO FURTHER, I WANT TO
START WITH THIS FIRST SITUATION,
DOUGLAS.
WE ARE IN WHAT WE MIGHT CALL AND
SOME OTHERS HAVE AN ASSASSINATION
CULTURE.
AND SO WHEN YOU PUT PEOPLE IN
DANGER AND YOU CAUSE A NO-GO
ZONE AROUND GOING TO HELP AGENTS
OR LAW ENFORCEMENT, YOU'RE
CREATING A PERFECT SCENE FOR
SOMEONE TO BE KILLED.
OH, YEAH.
AND IT'S BEEN HAPPENING FOR
YEARS, THIS.
WE'VE BEEN TALKING IN RECENT
WEEKS UNDERSTANDABLY ABOUT THE
ASSASSINATION CULTURE, THE
CULTURE OF ENCOURAGING POLITICAL
VIOLENCE IN THIS COUNTRY.
I DON'T THINK ANYONE HAS BEEN
MORE CONSISTENTLY ON THE
RECEIVING END OF THREATS OF
VIOLENCE THAN ICE AGENTS IN
THIS COUNTRY.
I'VE SEEN IT WITH MY OWN EYES.
IN 2020 I SAW I WAS UNDERCOVER
WITH ANTIFA IN PORTLAND AND I
JUST SAW THE WAY THEY WERE
BEHAVING TOWARDS THE ICE AGENTS.
THEY TRY TO BURN THEM ALIVE IN
THEIR BUILDINGS.
THEY SET LIGHT TO DUMPS THE
TRUCKS AND WHILE THEM INTO THE
DOORS IN THE HOPE THEY CAN'T GET
OUT.
NOW WE HAVE ROUTINELY THE DOXING
OF ANYONE WHO IS ICE AGENTS.
ICE AGENTS HAVING TO COVER THEIR
FACES FOR FEAR OF RETRIBUTION.
HIT LISTS OUT ONLINE WITH BOUNTIES
ON THE HEADS OF AGENTS.
THIS IS OBSCINE.
THIS SHOULD NOT BE HAPPENING IN
THIS COUNTRY.
THESE ARE FEDERAL EMPLOYEES.
NOT ONLY THE MASKING SITUATION,
YOU'VE GOT THE GOVERNOR OF
CALIFORNIA SAYING TAKE THE MASKS
OFF.
SO YOU'VE GOT THEM TRYING TO
PROTECT THEMSELVES AND THE
GOVERNOR OF A LARGE STATE THAT
HAS A LOT OF ILLEGAL ALIENS WHO
ARE COMMITTING CRIMES IN HIS
STATE, WANTING TO PROTECT THE
CRIMINALS OVER THE PEOPLE WHO
HAVE GONE TO TAKE BACK ORDER.
IT'S UNFATHOMABLE.
I'M GLAD YOU BRING UP 2020 AS
THEY ATTEMPTED TO LIGHT THAT
COURTHOUSE ON FIRE IN PORTLAND.
I'M READING THROUGH THE
EMERGENCY MOTION THAT DOJ FILED
TO THE NINTH CIRCUIT TO REVERSE
THE ORDER OF THE DISTRICT COURT
JUDGE THERE IN PORTLAND SAYING
YOU CAN'T DEPLOY THE NATIONAL
GUARD.
WHEN YOU GET TO PAGE SIX,
LISTEN TO THIS, THEY'RE STILL
DOING IT, DOUGLAS.
PROTESTERS REPEATEDLY TRIED TO
BURN DOWN THE PORTLAND ICE
OFFICE.
ONE PROTESTER LIT A FLAME, SET
FIRE TO MATERIALS, THE MOB THEN
PILED ON ADDITIONAL TENDER
ATTEMPTING TO STOKE THE FLAMES.
THAT'S JUST ONE OF SEVERAL
INCIDENTS THE GOVERNMENT POINTS
TO.
AND THEN YOU HAVE THE SITUATION
THAT IS, I JUST CAN'T EVEN WRAP
MY MIND AROUND.
PORTLAND POLICE NOT ALLOWED TO
GO INTO THIS BUBBLE.
THERE'S TWO LIAISON OFFICERS ON
EITHER SIDE.
AND THEN THEY GO INTO THE BUBBLE
TO ARREST NICK SORTER,
CONSERVATIVE JOURNALIST, FOR
DOING NOTHING, ACCORDING TO
HIM.
BUT DON'T GO INTO STOP THIS KIND
OF STUFF.
THIS IS WHY PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS
TO STEP IN.
AND JUST, I WOULD SAY THIS, YOU
KNOW, I SPOKE ON SATURDAY, SATURDAY
IN AMERICA, WITH TOM HOMEN.
AND I SAID TO TOM, WHAT'S
HAPPENING IN PORTLAND, THE
STAND DOWN OF THE POLICE THAT
WE'RE SEEING, IS IT HAPPENING
IN CHICAGO?
AND THIS WAS RIGHT BEFORE THIS
INCIDENT HAPPENED.
AND HE SAID TO ME, CHICAGO,
NEW YORK, PORTLAND, IT'S NOT
THE RANK AND FILE POLICE
OFFICERS.
THEY WANT TO DO THEIR JOB.
IT IS THE DEMOCRATIC LAWMAKERS
ON TOP CREATING THIS DANGEROUS
SITUATION.
WELL, AND IF YOU DO EVENTUALLY
HAVE TO SEND IN LAW ENFORCEMENT
OFFICERS, YOU HAVE ENDANGERED
EVERYBODY'S LIFE AT THAT POINT.
BECAUSE NOW THEY'RE WALKING
INTO SOMETHING THAT'S ALREADY
COOKING WITH GAS.
ABSOLUTELY, HARRIS.
AND FOR THOSE OPPOSING WHAT ICE
IS DOING, WHAT'S THE
ALTERNATIVE?
JUST ALLOW TERRORISTS, CARTEL
MEMBERS, CHILD PREDATORS TO
REMAIN IN AMERICA?
I MEAN, IS THAT WHAT THESE
GOVERNORS ARE ADVOCATING FOR?
I MEAN, ESSENTIALLY, IT IS.
AND DOUGLAS, I'M GLAD YOU
MENTIONED THE BOUNTY STORY.
I WAS CO-HOSTING FOX AND FRIENDS
YESTERDAY WHEN SECRETARY NOEM
BROKE THAT NEWS.
SHE SAID SOME OF OUR ICE AGENTS
AND OFFICERS HAVE BOUNIES PUT
OUT FOR THEIR HEADS, 2,000 TO
KIDNAP, 10,000 TO KILL.
THEIR PICTURES ARE BEING SENT
AROUND NETWORKS.
I ASKED HER THE FOLLOW-UP
QUESTION, WHO IS BEHIND IT?
WHO IS FUNDING THESE BOUNTIES?
AND SHE SAID CARTELS AND
THEY ARE WORKING ON A WHOLE
GOVERNMENT APPROACH ALONG WITH
THE TREASURY DEPARTMENT TO TRY
TO GET TO THE BOTTOM OF WHO IS
FUNDING THESE RIOTS.
SHE SAID SHE WAS IN CHICAGO A
COUPLE OF DAYS AGO.
THEY ALL HAVE THE SAME MASKS.
THEY ALL HAVE THE SAME SIGNS.
INEVITATELY, WE KNOW WE HAVE A
DOMESTIC TERRORISM PROBLEM
BECAUSE THAT IS ESSENTIALLY WHAT
IS HAPPENING IN THESE CITIES.
THEY ARE USING VIOLENCE TO TRY
TO CHANGE OUR GOVERNMENT'S
APPROACH, GOVERNMENT POLICY.
BUT HOW MUCH OVERLAP IS THERE
WITH FOREIGN TERRORISM?
AND I THINK WITH SOME OF THESE
INVESTIGATIONS, HOPEFULLY WE GET
TO THE BOTTOM OF THAT.
YEAH, I WANT TO GO BACK FOR
JUST A SECOND.
ILLINOIS GOVERNOR J.B.
PRITZKER DISMISSED THE DANGER
THAT AGENTS ARE FACING.
HIS STATE HAS FILED A LAWSUIT
AGAINST THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION
FOR DEPLOYING THE NATIONAL
GUARD.
LET'S WATCH.